15dollarstore.com 2007-10-11

# 15DOLLARSTORE.COM - Privacy Statement

|  | 

Privacy Statement: Your Personal Information

**THE15DOLLARSTORE.COM** values its customers and respects their privacy. We collect customer information in an effort to improve our customers' shopping experience and to communicate with our customers about our products, service's, contests and promotions. We recognize that we must maintain and use customer information responsibly. We do not sell or rent the information you provide to us to any outside companies or third parties. 

If our information practices change in the future, we will let you know before we use your information in a manner not previously disclosed in our privacy policy by posting the policy changes on our website or by communicating directly with you. At that time, you will have the opportunity to opt out of any new use of your information. If you have any questions about our privacy policy, you can always contact **THE15DOLLARSTORE.COM's** customer service in any of the following ways:

1\. Send us an email: [support@the15dollarstore.com](mailto:support@the15dollarstore.com)

2\. Write to us at  
   THE15DOLLARSTORE.COM  
   1160 Sandhill Avenue   
   Carson , CA 90746

**How do I know my order information is secure?**  
Providing a safe and secure environment for your order information is our top priority. **THE15DOLLARSTORE.COM** protects the security of your online transaction by taking advantage of Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology. When you order, your credit card information is secure. **THE15DOLLARSTORE.COM** uses digital certificates provided by Equifax which are required for SSL, the industry standard for encryption. SSL technology encrypts data allowing only **THE15DOLLARSTORE.COM** to decode your information and helps to create a secure environment for transactions on the internet.

To check the security of your connection when checking out, look at the lower right-hand corner of your browser window after accessing the server. If you see an unbroken key or a closed lock (depending on your browser), then SSL is active. You can also double-check by looking at the URL line of your browser. When accessing a secure server, the first characters of the site address will change from "http to "https."

To further protect your security, we suggest you close your browser window after you have finished your visit, especially if you are using a computer shared by others.

**THE15DOLLARSTORE.COM** website may contain links to other sites that are not under our control. These websites have their own policies regarding privacy. You should review those policies before visiting the websites. We have no responsibility for linked websites, and we provide these links solely for the convenience and information of our visitors.

**Browser Compatibility**  
Our technical team makes every effort to ensure the site will be compatible with every browser, but **THE15DOLLARSTORE.COM** site is currently optimized for the latest versions of Internet Explorer, Netscape, Safari, FireFox browsers, with a screen resolution set to 1024 X 768. Javascript and Cookies must be enabled. Please see your browser's help section for more information.
